<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>

<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Selected Works from Jeremy Bunting</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Selected Works from Jeremy Bunting</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2018 21:27:25 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2018 21:27:25 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resume/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;resume here&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2018 21:27:12 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;./uploads/2018/02/21/Bunting_Jeremy_v4-2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A tech nerd with the eye of a designer, Jeremy&amp;rsquo;s work has helped push clients to do the unexpected. His deep tech knowledge enables businesses to bridge physical into digital and back again. Guiding projects from Cisco, Target and an outrageous VR event for Elton John, his acumen in steering teams to get inventive is his greatest asset. A maker through and through, Jeremy&amp;rsquo;s goal is to make any digital project project feel tangible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A Connecticut transplant, he and his wife Jess live in Orange County with his two daughters Maisy and Margot and far too many Raspberry Pis.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Calphalon Signature Series</title>
      <link>/project/calphalon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2018 21:26:51 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/calphalon/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;While still in college, I designed, developed and patented a line of cookware for nationwide cookware manufacturer Calphalon.  The series of cookware features a non-stick surface, rubber overmolded stay-cool handles and a modern understated aesthetic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While working at The Calphalon Group, I developed this line using state of the art CAD and 3D printing technologies, as well as traditional product design skills.  This background allows me to approach interactive design and development from a fresh, rare perspective.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This line was &lt;a href=&#34;http://bit.ly/bkZTA2&#34;&gt;patented&lt;/a&gt; and was available exclusively at Kohl&amp;rsquo;s Department Stores.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Popsecret Popover</title>
      <link>/project/popsecret-popover/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2018 21:26:27 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/popsecret-popover/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;./uploads/2018/02/13/target001.png&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pop Secret was after a new way for people to enjoy movies together. Deutsch designed social organization tool called PopOver for Pop Secret&amp;rsquo;s loyal customers and movie devotees.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The application allows for friends to send one another an invitation to a movie night hosted at someone&amp;rsquo;s house. The app allows for friends to organize the movie of the night, set a theme, organize snacks and get together to enjoy some popcorn and fun.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The application integrated tightly with a custom movie information API, Facebook and various other social platforms. This was a responsive Backbone.js application designed to work across mobile platforms, and from mobile to desktop and tablet.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VW Smiledrive</title>
      <link>/project/vw-smiledrive/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2018 21:26:16 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/vw-smiledrive/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;VW SmileDrive is a way for you and your friends to compile your favorite parts of a road trip you take in your Volkswagen vehicle. The app was designed to capture the moments of a road trip that you don&amp;rsquo;t want to forget, even if it&amp;rsquo;s not a Volkswagen. The app would allow you to capture a cohesive picture timeline of your trip, play &amp;lsquo;punch-dub&amp;rsquo; on the way, and earn badges for driving in certain conditions. The companion website uses many Google Plus, Picasa and Google Maps APIs to render your custom road trip story in a beautiful, responsive interface.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Within 3 months of launch, the SmileDrive application amassed 230,000 drives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The application and the launch were part of &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.artcopycode.com/campaign/volkswagen&#34;&gt;Google&amp;rsquo;s Art Copy and Code Project&lt;/a&gt; and a joint venture with &lt;a href=&#34;http://thisisgrow.com/awards/vw/smiledrive/&#34;&gt;Grow&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My responsibility was development of the app&amp;rsquo;s website, animations and consulting on the desktop site companion to the app.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VW Find a Match</title>
      <link>/project/vw-find-a-match/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2018 21:26:06 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/vw-find-a-match/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Volkswagen&amp;rsquo;s 3.0 release of their website is a landmark achievement for Deutsch LA and the automotive industry. With a history of large, hard to use websites, entrenched technology, and slow moving clients, this site signals a sea-change in how agencies build large corporate sites.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Deutsch LA engineered a brand new, end to end system with partners worldwide to surface VW vehicles in a brand new light. With vehicle specific artwork, specifications and beautiful renders, this site shows Volkswagen vehicles in a way that made the entire auto industry pay attention. This site garnered major attention from &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.fastcocreate.com/3030032/the-new-vwcom-takes-a-page-from-online-dating-to-help-you-find-a-car&#34;&gt;Fast Company&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;http://digiday.com/brands/vw-new-site/&#34;&gt;Digiday&lt;/a&gt;. The site has been a huge success and has triggered an industry-wide refocus on digital efforts far beyond Volkswagen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the technical side, the site was built with a large, enterprise CMS, using Backbone applications for single page applications across the site. I functioned as technical lead for the Find A Match component and lead a team-wide refactoring effort. The refactor focused on improving performance, stability and setting the team up for long-term success as the site scaled over time. I also engineered a shared data controller to manage the inventory data across all front-end components in the site in an organized way. The front-end uses an event aggregator pattern to share data and signal events across many standalone, decoupled components.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This site has won multiple awards, including a &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.oneclub.org/#olmag=/_ajax/archive/?action=arc_work%26value=23022%26rndm=817&#34;&gt;Bronze Pencil in the 2015 One Show&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The code I wrote for these components is in production use today.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vivint</title>
      <link>/project/vivint/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2018 21:25:57 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/vivint/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Vivint is a home automation and security company. Vivint approached Deutsch to develop a front-end experience for their new Vivint Sky home automation platform.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My front-end team of 4 and I developed a series of complex pages for the Vivint technical team to use as a baseline for all new website efforts. The site development was completed inside Vivint&amp;rsquo;s custom CMS. All pages were compiled using Gulp, Compass and Node.js, in order to provide solid performance, optimized assets and a pain-free workflow. This workflow also provided live-reloading the browser, generating sprite sheets and source maps, and flagging code style issues before code was pushed to the repo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our contributions included a 3D rendering sequence and a parallax single page scrolling site that highlighted all major features of the Vivint Sky system. The site serves as a guideline for Vivint&amp;rsquo;s future digital work.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Target College Styler</title>
      <link>/project/target-college-styler/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2018 21:25:35 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/target-college-styler/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Target has a major effort behind the back-to-school timeframe every year. Many students, parents and those buying for kids moving to college, rely on Target for stylish, affordable and fun college accessories.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Deutsch LA envisioned a new kind of tool for prospective college students planning their first dorm room. Heading to college is an uncomfortable time for many college kids. Questions surface like &amp;lsquo;What&amp;rsquo;s my roommate going to be like?&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;how do I do laundry?&amp;rsquo;. Because of this discomfort, Deutsch designed a new platform for showing college kids how amazing their new environment can be, and help break the ice with their new roommate. Target College Styler is a tool that allows you to connect your social media account, answer some simple quiz questions, and get amazing suggestions for what their space could look like and how they could vibe with their new roommate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The College Styler platform is a mobile first web application, built using Backbone and a custom Codeigniter implementation. The application pulls in social media content, pulls dominant colors and helps you put together a dorm room that fits your likes, color palette, even how you like to eat breakfast. Using dominant colors from your instagram feed clues the application into what colors you could style your dorm room in. Not only is this site smooth and fast on the major mobile platforms, it&amp;rsquo;s also accessible to &lt;a href=&#34;[http://www.w3.org/WAI/intro/wcag&#34;&gt;WCAG 2.0 Level AA&lt;/a&gt; compliance on desktop, mobile and tablet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The site has been featured in &lt;a href=&#34;http://adage.com/article/acxiom/target-taps-millenial-market-back-school-push/299675/&#34;&gt;AdAge&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;http://creativity-online.com/work/target-made-for-u-college-styler/42845&#34;&gt;Creativity Online&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I managed the international development team, took part in the original SWAT team that generated this concept, wrote several parts of the application, managed the infrastructure, and helped push the application through the QA process.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Really allows us to connect to those millennial guests ~ &lt;a href=&#34;http://adage.com/article/acxiom/target-taps-millenial-market-back-school-push/299675/&#34;&gt;AdAge&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Target is making back-to-school shopping personal ~ &lt;a href=&#34;http://creativity-online.com/work/target-made-for-u-college-styler/42845&#34;&gt;Creativity Online&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elton Farewell VR</title>
      <link>/project/elton/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2018 21:25:16 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/elton/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cisco Portals</title>
      <link>/project/cisco-portals/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2017 00:38:21 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/cisco-portals/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;./uploads/2018/02/20/2016-08-24.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>deutsch.com</title>
      <link>/project/deutsch.com/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2016 13:29:18 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/deutsch.com/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Deutsch&amp;rsquo;s website was woefully out of date and built on old, inflexible technology. I was tasked with a new systems architecture to handle a ground up rebuild of the agency website. This included a portfolio, integration with an HR system and&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VW Unleash Your Rrr</title>
      <link>/project/vw-unleash-your-rrr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jul 2015 21:25:47 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/vw-unleash-your-rrr/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Volkswagen Unleash Your Rrr project was a new breed of technology for Deutsch. The app records your voice and your face as you imitate the Volkswagen Golf R screaming around the track at top speed. The Deutsch team came up with a set of techniques and technologies in order to break up those sounds dynamically, analyze them, and then assemble some carefully selected video content to match your performance. What you end up with is a customized video complete with your voice with clips of the Golf R screaming around the track that matches your voice, timing and energy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We used combination of digital signals processing and deep machine learning to analyze your performance. We then stitch together an optimized, YouTube ready video so you can share it out to all your friends. The concept is simple, the UI is extremely animated and engaging, and it&amp;rsquo;s very fun to use. I served as tech lead for the primary feature build, systems architecture, technical documentation, video pipeline and dev team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There was a very small team for this project and it was a challenging, fun project to build. &lt;a href=&#34;http://rrr.vw.com&#34;&gt;Take a spin&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Press/Awards&lt;/em&gt; •
&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.thefwa.com/site/unleash-your-rrrr&#34;&gt;FWA Site of the Day&lt;/a&gt; •
&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.adweek.com/adfreak/make-bunch-vrooming-and-squealing-car-noises-and-vw-will-turn-it-video-165861&#34;&gt;AdWeek&lt;/a&gt; •
&lt;a href=&#34;http://creativity-online.com/work/volkswagen-unleash-your-rrrr-michael-winslow-demo/42684&#34;&gt;Creativity Online&lt;/a&gt; •
&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.businessinsider.com/volkswagen-golf-r-voice-controlled-campaign-2015-7&#34;&gt;Business Insider&lt;/a&gt; •
&lt;a href=&#34;http://thenextweb.com/shareables/2015/07/15/vroom-vroom/&#34;&gt;TNW&lt;/a&gt; •
&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.fastcocreate.com/3048595/you-control-this-new-vw-ad-by-making-your-own-ridiculous-car-noises&#34;&gt;Fast Co.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wendy&#39;s Wendythreads</title>
      <link>/project/wendys-wendythreads/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2012 21:26:40 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/wendys-wendythreads/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Wendy Threads is an interactive T-shirt builder for the Wendy&amp;rsquo;s Restaurant chain. Wendy Threads launched with a street team promotion in Times Square and hit 100,000 visits and 8,000 T-shirt submissions within 24 hours of launch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This app features easy to use design tools and a library of 300 creative assets. The number of assets, great performance, and ease of use has prompted over 12,000 T-shirt submissions in the first week.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My responsibility for the app was the front end app architecture, the gallery, social integration and API communication. The gallery uses a blitted rendering technique to smoothly handle 800 gallery tiles with fast frame rates. This app uses an MVCS architecture facilitated by Robotlegs and Swift Suspenders.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drafting Stool</title>
      <link>/project/drafting-stool/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2006 21:26:58 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/drafting-stool/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A completely self-designed, modeled and fabricated drafting stool made for my own physiological dimensions.  The stool was designed for easy movement around the studio, light weight and comfortable use while drawing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Designed with the playful nature of a bicycle in mind, the stool was envisioned with wheels making the essential &amp;ldquo;scoot forward&amp;rdquo; into the drafting desk a fully considered movement.  The weight of the movement gets transferred to the wheels making the slide forward silent and effortless.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There were 3 models of this stool before the final execution.  The base is aircraft grade aluminum.  The seatpan is birch wood with a zebrano wood veneer finish and the wheels are polyurethane/cast aluminum combination. I used this stool for a semester in the studio.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>