<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Selected Works from Jeremy Bunting</title>
    <link>https://work.jeremybunting.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Selected Works from Jeremy Bunting</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2018 21:27:25 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://work.jeremybunting.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>https://work.jeremybunting.com/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2018 21:27:25 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://work.jeremybunting.com/resume/</guid>
      <description>resume here</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://work.jeremybunting.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2018 21:27:12 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://work.jeremybunting.com/about/</guid>
      <description>about section here</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drafting Stool</title>
      <link>https://work.jeremybunting.com/project/drafting-stool/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2018 21:26:58 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://work.jeremybunting.com/project/drafting-stool/</guid>
      <description>A completely self-designed, modeled and fabricated drafting stool made for my own physiological dimensions. The stool was designed for easy movement around the studio, light weight and comfortable use while drawing.
Designed with the playful nature of a bicycle in mind, the stool was envisioned with wheels making the essential &amp;ldquo;scoot forward&amp;rdquo; into the drafting desk a fully considered movement. The weight of the movement gets transferred to the wheels making the slide forward silent and effortless.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Calphalon Signature Series</title>
      <link>https://work.jeremybunting.com/project/calphalon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2018 21:26:51 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://work.jeremybunting.com/project/calphalon/</guid>
      <description>While still in college, I designed, developed and patented a line of cookware for nationwide cookware manufacturer Calphalon. The series of cookware features a non-stick surface, rubber overmolded stay-cool handles and a modern understated aesthetic.
While working at The Calphalon Group, I developed this line using state of the art CAD and 3D printing technologies, as well as traditional product design skills. This background allows me to approach interactive design and development from a fresh, rare perspective.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wendy&#39;s Wendythreads</title>
      <link>https://work.jeremybunting.com/project/wendys-wendythreads/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2018 21:26:40 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://work.jeremybunting.com/project/wendys-wendythreads/</guid>
      <description>Wendy Threads is an interactive T-shirt builder for the Wendy&amp;rsquo;s Restaurant chain. Wendy Threads launched with a street team promotion in Times Square and hit 100,000 visits and 8,000 T-shirt submissions within 24 hours of launch.
This app features easy to use design tools and a library of 300 creative assets. The number of assets, great performance, and ease of use has prompted over 12,000 T-shirt submissions in the first week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Popsecret Popover</title>
      <link>https://work.jeremybunting.com/project/popsecret-popover/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2018 21:26:27 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://work.jeremybunting.com/project/popsecret-popover/</guid>
      <description>Pop Secret was after a new way for people to enjoy movies together. Deutsch designed social organization tool called PopOver for Pop Secret&amp;rsquo;s loyal customers and movie devotees.
The application allows for friends to send one another an invitation to a movie night hosted at someone&amp;rsquo;s house. The app allows for friends to organize the movie of the night, set a theme, organize snacks and get together to enjoy some popcorn and fun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VW Smiledrive</title>
      <link>https://work.jeremybunting.com/project/vw-smiledrive/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2018 21:26:16 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://work.jeremybunting.com/project/vw-smiledrive/</guid>
      <description>VW SmileDrive is a way for you and your friends to compile your favorite parts of a road trip you take in your Volkswagen vehicle. The app was designed to capture the moments of a road trip that you don&amp;rsquo;t want to forget, even if it&amp;rsquo;s not a Volkswagen. The app would allow you to capture a cohesive picture timeline of your trip, play &amp;lsquo;punch-dub&amp;rsquo; on the way, and earn badges for driving in certain conditions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VW Find a Match</title>
      <link>https://work.jeremybunting.com/project/vw-find-a-match/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2018 21:26:06 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://work.jeremybunting.com/project/vw-find-a-match/</guid>
      <description>Volkswagen&amp;rsquo;s 3.0 release of their website is a landmark achievement for Deutsch LA and the automotive industry. With a history of large, hard to use websites, entrenched technology, and slow moving clients, this site signals a sea-change in how agencies build large corporate sites.
Deutsch LA engineered a brand new, end to end system with partners worldwide to surface VW vehicles in a brand new light. With vehicle specific artwork, specifications and beautiful renders, this site shows Volkswagen vehicles in a way that made the entire auto industry pay attention.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vivint</title>
      <link>https://work.jeremybunting.com/project/vivint/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2018 21:25:57 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://work.jeremybunting.com/project/vivint/</guid>
      <description>Vivint is a home automation and security company. Vivint approached Deutsch to develop a front-end experience for their new Vivint Sky home automation platform.
My front-end team of 4 and I developed a series of complex pages for the Vivint technical team to use as a baseline for all new website efforts. The site development was completed inside Vivint&amp;rsquo;s custom CMS. All pages were compiled using Gulp, Compass and Node.js, in order to provide solid performance, optimized assets and a pain-free workflow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VW Unleash Your Rrr</title>
      <link>https://work.jeremybunting.com/project/vw-unleash-your-rrr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2018 21:25:47 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://work.jeremybunting.com/project/vw-unleash-your-rrr/</guid>
      <description>The Volkswagen Unleash Your Rrr project was a new breed of technology for Deutsch. The app records your voice and your face as you imitate the Volkswagen Golf R screaming around the track at top speed. The Deutsch team came up with a set of techniques and technologies in order to break up those sounds dynamically, analyze them, and then assemble some carefully selected video content to match your performance. What you end up with is a customized video complete with your voice with clips of the Golf R screaming around the track that matches your voice, timing and energy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Target College Styler</title>
      <link>https://work.jeremybunting.com/project/target-college-styler/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2018 21:25:35 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://work.jeremybunting.com/project/target-college-styler/</guid>
      <description>Target has a major effort behind the back-to-school timeframe every year. Many students, parents and those buying for kids moving to college, rely on Target for stylish, affordable and fun college accessories.
Deutsch LA envisioned a new kind of tool for prospective college students planning their first dorm room. Heading to college is an uncomfortable time for many college kids. Questions surface like &amp;lsquo;What&amp;rsquo;s my roommate going to be like?&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;how do I do laundry?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elton Farewell VR</title>
      <link>https://work.jeremybunting.com/project/elton/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2018 21:25:16 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://work.jeremybunting.com/project/elton/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>